export const chapter = "Chapter - 11: Forms of Verbs";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question:
            "What is the Present form (I form) of the verb in the sentence 'Megha sings a song.'?",
          optionA: "sing",
          optionB: "sang",
          optionC: "sung",
          correctAnswer: "sing",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which form of the verb is used in the sentence 'Megha sang a song.'?",
          optionA: "I form",
          optionB: "II form",
          optionC: "III form",
          correctAnswer: "II form",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In the sentence 'Megha has sung a song,' which form of the verb is the Past Participle?",
          optionA: "I form",
          optionB: "II form",
          optionC: "III form",
          correctAnswer: "III form",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What is the Present Participle form (ing form) of the verb in the sentence 'Megha is singing a song.'?",
          optionA: "sing",
          optionB: "sang",
          optionC: "singing",
          correctAnswer: "singing",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Identify the tense used in the sentence 'Megha sings a song.'",
          optionA: "Simple Present Tense",
          optionB: "Simple Past Tense",
          optionC: "Present Participle Tense",
          correctAnswer: "Simple Present Tense",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which tense is employed in the sentence 'Megha sang a song.'?",
          optionA: "Present Perfect Tense",
          optionB: "Simple Past Tense",
          optionC: "Past Perfect Tense",
          correctAnswer: "Simple Past Tense",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What does the sentence 'Megha has sung a song.' represent in terms of tense?",
          optionA: "Simple Present Tense",
          optionB: "Present Perfect Tense",
          optionC: "Past Perfect Tense",
          correctAnswer: "Present Perfect Tense",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In the sentence 'Megha is singing a song,' what kind of form does the verb take?",
          optionA: "Present Participle form",
          optionB: "Past Participle form",
          optionC: "Future Participle form",
          correctAnswer: "Present Participle form",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which form of the verb is used in the sentence 'Megha has sung a song.'?",
          optionA: "I form",
          optionB: "II form",
          optionC: "III form",
          correctAnswer: "III form",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What is the verb form in the sentence 'Megha is singing a song.'?",
          optionA: "Present Tense",
          optionB: "Past Tense",
          optionC: "Present Participle Tense",
          correctAnswer: "Present Participle Tense",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blank with correct option:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question:
            "Some Verbs show existence; for example:\nI am a __________.\n",
          optionA: "person",
          optionB: "girl",
          optionC: "boy",
          correctAnswer: "boy",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Some Verbs show action. They are doing words; for example:\nAlways speak __________ truth.\n",
          optionA: "a",
          optionB: "the",
          optionC: "an",
          correctAnswer: "the",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Some Verbs can be made up of more than one word; for example:\nAnjali is dancing __________ the room.\n",
          optionA: "at",
          optionB: "on",
          optionC: "in",
          correctAnswer: "in",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In these sentences, the Verbs have two words: is dancing, was running, were playing, and __________ respectively.\n",
          optionA: "jump",
          optionB: "climb",
          optionC: "rise",
          correctAnswer: "rise",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The words: is, was, were, and will are helping the Main Verbs to express their meanings respectively. So, they are called __________ Verbs.\n",
          optionA: "Primary",
          optionB: "Action",
          optionC: "Helping",
          correctAnswer: "Helping",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Some Verbs can have even three or four words; for example:\nThe girls will be dancing on __________ stage.\n",
          optionA: "a",
          optionB: "an",
          optionC: "the",
          correctAnswer: "the",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In these sentences, the Helping Verbs are will be and shall have been, and the Main Verbs are dancing and playing.\nThe Helping Verbs are used to assist the Main Verbs in expressing their meanings. So, they are called __________ Verbs.\n",
          optionA: "Primary",
          optionB: "Action",
          optionC: "Helping",
          correctAnswer: "Helping",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The Verbs can be used in different times. They can show the present, past, or future time. These times are called __________.\n",
          optionA: "Clauses",
          optionB: "Phrases",
          optionC: "Tenses",
          correctAnswer: "Tenses",
        },
        {
          question:
            "When something happens now, it is in the Present Tense; for example:\nThe girl is in __________ bed.\n",
          optionA: "a",
          optionB: "an",
          optionC: "the",
          correctAnswer: "the",
        },
        {
          question:
            "When something happened in the past, it is in the Past Tense; for example:\nHe was in __________ jail.\n",
          optionA: "an",
          optionB: "the",
          optionC: "a",
          correctAnswer: "the",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question: "Megha sings a song.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "Anjali was running in the park.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "The cat is sleeping on the roof.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "The girls will be dancing on the stage.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "He has written a letter.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "They were playing football.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "The sun rises in the east.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "The children are playing in the playground.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "She had completed her homework.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "You will have spoken the truth.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
